<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project on IN104 - MiniWolfram</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/IN104/project/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project on IN104 - MiniWolfram</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/IN104/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>First step</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/IN104/project/first-step/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/IN104/project/first-step/index.html</guid>
      <description>Download the project files You can download the provided files directly from the GitHub repository by using the following command:
git clone https://github.com/TurtleSmoke/IN104.gitCreate a new repository After downloading the repository, the next step is to create a new private repository on your GitHub account. Then, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to update the remote URL of your local repository to link it with the newly created repository. This can be done by executing the following commands:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Description</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/IN104/project/description/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/IN104/project/description/index.html</guid>
      <description>Note Before starting the project, please follow the instructions in the first step to download the provided files and create a new repository.
Overview The project is focused on creating a simplified version of Wolfram Alpha starting with the implementation of a basic calculator. This baseline calculator must be capable of handling the following operations:
Addition Subtraction Multiplication Division Modulus Additionally, the calculator must handle parentheses and spaces within expressions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provided files</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/IN104/project/given-code/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/IN104/project/given-code/index.html</guid>
      <description>Provided files To help you get started, we have provided a utils file containing the following structures:
TokenType: An enumeration representing the different types of tokens. Token: A structure representing a token. TokenQueue: A structure representing a queue of tokens. TokenStack: A structure representing a stack of tokens. Token types The TokenType enumeration contains the following token types:
typedef enum { NUMBER = 0, ADD, SUB, MUL, DIV, MOD, LEFT_PAREN, RIGHT_PAREN, } TokenType;You can use this enumeration to identify the type of each token in the input string.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Additional Resources</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/IN104/project/additional-resources/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/IN104/project/additional-resources/index.html</guid>
      <description>Additional resources Here are some additional resources that you may find useful for this project:
Example of good README Why you should use Git How to correctly commit Commits convention Test-Driven Development What is test-driven development (TDD)? Test Driven Development Unit testing Better Unit Testing Formatting your code Pre-commit hooks </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>